findrsearch.com 2016-02-23

# Uninstall | Findr

### System Requirements

Windows XP/Vista/7 32-bit & 64-bit

## Findr Toolbar and FindrSearch.com Privacy Policy

BonJoyTM Software (“We” or “BonJoy”) know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) and other information We gather when you are downloading, installing or using our FindrTM Search Toolbar (the “Findr Toolbar”) or accessing the Findr Toolbar websites (“Site” or “Sites”).

In addition, this Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of Personal Information and other information We gather when you use the Findr Toolbar or by using any other services or products on or through our Site.

By visiting our Sites or using our Findr Toolbar, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. Please note this policy does not apply to (and We are not responsible for) the practices of companies that We do not own or control or to individuals We do not employ or manage. When utilizing third party sites or software products, you should read the relevant privacy policies of those third parties for information regarding their privacy practices.

  1. To better explain what information We collect, and how We use the information We collect, We have broken out our Privacy Policy into the following sections: 

    1. Section 2: WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY. This section explains what information We collect from:
    2. (a) users who install the Findr Toolbar; and
    3. (b) visitors to our Sites.
    4. Section 3: HOW WE SHARE OR USE INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED. This section explains how We use your information, and why, as well as if and how We share your information.
    5. Sections 4-8: These sections discuss various topics, including how We protect any information We collect, how you can update any information you share with us, our compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, our storage and use of information from users outside the United States, and how We may alert you of any changes to this Privacy Policy.

  2. To better explain what information We collect, and how We use the information We collect, We have broken out our Privacy Policy into the following sections: 

    1. USERS WHO INSTALL THE FINDR TOOLBAR.

If you are a user who has installed the Findr Toolbar, the following types of information are collected:

Usage Information. When you use the Findr Toolbar, search functionality and other services are enabled through the Findr Toolbar by a third party search provider (“Search Provider”). In using the Findr Toolbar, such Search Provider may collect information about the websites you visit and the advertisements that you see on those websites, the searches you perform, the ways in which you use various Findr Toolbar features (including whether the Findr Toolbar is still installed on your computer), and the pages you view. For more information, please visit <http://support.infospace.com/privacy/> or [http://www.dogpile.com/support/privacypolicy.](http://www.dogpile.com/support/privacypolicy)

Third Party Services and Sites. If, through your use of the Sites or the Findr Toolbar, you have installed a product provided by a third party, or have accessed third party sites or services, then such third parties may also collect information regarding your usage of such sites or services. Any information collected by a third party provider is governed by such third party providers’ privacy policies. These third party sites may also place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Information from you. We do not exercise control over any third party sites that our Sites or the Findr Toolbar or other third party application, may link to.

    2. WEBSITE VISITOR

If you are a visitor to our Sites, We collect the following types of information:

Cookies. When you visit our Sites, We will send you a cookie which is stored on your computer and allows us to uniquely identify it. We use cookies to help us better understand our users, which allows us to improve our products and services. This data may include storing user preferences and product utilization information such as number of visitors, average time spent on pages, features used, and other information which helps us determine which features are most important to you and working effectively.

Logs When you visit our Sites, We capture and store the data that your computer sends us. This data may include your browser type, language, Internet Protocol address, the date and time of your request and the cookie that helps us identify your computer.

Usage Information. Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Sites and its components. We only use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of our Sites, products or services so that We can improve the performance of our products and services.

Communication or Information You Provide. Any time you send us a communication, We may keep this communication so that We can respond to your requests or inquiries and help improve our services to you. We may also store any information you provide to us through the Sites or through any communications you send to us, or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected may include your name and email address. The Personal Information you provide may be used to help us communication with you or improve our Sites or services.

Third Party Applications. We may make available third party applications or services through the Sites or the Findr Toolbar, including third party applications that access third party sites or services. The information collected when you enable or use search functionality or other services through the Findr Toolbar is processed under the Findr Toolbar’s Search Provider’s Privacy Policy at http://www.findrsearch.com/privacy-policy/. Information collected when you enable or use other third party applications or services provided by a third party provider is governed by such third party providers’ privacy policies.

Other Sites. This Privacy Policy only applies to the Sites. We do not exercise control over any third party sites that the Sites, or that the Findr Toolbar or other third party application, may link to. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Information from you.

  3.     1. For Findr Toolbar Users.

Any information collected by the Search Provider is governed by the Search Provider’s privacy policy located at: <http://support.infospace.com/privacy/> or <http://www.dogpile.com/support/privacypolicy>.

    2. For all Personal Information and other Information We Collect. We may also share or use your Personal Information or other information as follows:

      * Protection of BonJoy and Others. We may share your Personal Information and other information if We have a good faith belief that it is required to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (3) enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy and/or any other agreements between you and BonJoy, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of BonJoy, its visitors, users and/or the public. 
      * Business Transfers. If BonJoy or substantially all of its assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event that BonJoy goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that would be transferred to, or acquired by, a third party acquiror. Accordingly, We may transfer or assign all the information We have collected as part of a merger, acquisition, sale or other change of control. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror may continue to use your Personal Information and other information as set forth in this policy. 
      * Non-Personal Information. We may share your non-personally identifiable information with partners and other third parties for the purpose of helping us improve the Findr Toolbar and the overall performance of our products and services, or allow us to provide recommendations. For example, utilizing data to determine the probability that a consumer will enjoy the Findr Toolbar. 
      * With Your Consent. Except as set forth above, We will only share your Personal Information with third parties with your prior consent.

  4. 4\. INFORMATION SECURITY

We endeavor to take security measures to guard against unauthorized access to the systems where We store your data. This includes internal reviews of our data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures and physical security measures. However, despite the measures We take We cannot warrant the security of any information provided to us. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

  5. 5\. CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), We will not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and guardians to be familiar with the websites that their children visit. The Federal Trade Commission ("FTC") regulates the means by which website operators collect and use Personal Information from children under 13, pursuant to COPPA. For more information about COPPA and children's on-line privacy in general, visit the FTC's website at [www.ftc.gov/privacy](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy). For safety tips on privacy visit [www.OnGuardOnline.gov](http://www.onguardonline.gov/).

  6. 6\. USERS LOCATED OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES

Our Sites, the Findr Toolbar, and other services and products are hosted by servers located in the United States. If you are located outside the United States, your information will be transferred to our servers in the United States. By visiting our Sites, or using the Findr Toolbar or any of our services or products, you consent to the transfer, storage and use of your information in the United States.

  7. 7\. POLICY CHANGES

We may make changes to this policy from time to time. If We make changes in the way We use Personal Information, We will notify you by posting an announcement on our site or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses our site or services after such changes have been first posted.

If you have feedback, questions or concerns contact us at Privacy, c/o BonJoy Software, 510 Market St, Ste 301, San Diego, CA 92101 or email us at [privacy@bonjoy.com](mailto:privacy@bonjoy.com).

Effective Date of this Privacy Policy: July XX, 2012
